[
    {
        "question": "What is the correct logical operator for 'and'?",
        "answers": [
            "and",
            "or",
            "not",
            "&"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which logical operator means 'or'?",
        "answers": [
            "or",
            "and",
            "not",
            "xor"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output of (True and False);",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "None",
            "Error"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the command (5 > 3) and (2 < 4) return?",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "None",
            "Error"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "How to write an if statement in Python;",
        "answers": [
            "if x > 0:",
            "if x > 0 then",
            "if (x > 0)",
            "if x > 0 do:"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
        
            "question": "What is the output of the command (True or False) and False;",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False",
                "None",
                "Error"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        },
        {
        
            "question": "What is the output of not (False or True)?",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False",
                "None",
                "Error"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        }    
        ,
        {
            "question": "What does the condition (4 == 4) and (2 > 3) return?",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False",
                "None",
                "Error"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a logical operator?",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "or",
                "not",
                "add"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct syntax for an if-else statement in Python?",
            "answers": [
                "if x > 0: else:",
                "if (x > 0) {}",
                "if x > 0: pass else: pass",
                "if x > 0: pass else: pass"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of bool(\"\");",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False",
                "None",
                "Error"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which operator is used to check if two values ​​are different?",
            "answers": [
                "==",
                "!=",
                "<>",
                "=~"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": " Which of the following expressions correctly checks if a number x is between 10 and 20 (inclusive) in Python?",
            "answers": [
                "if x > 10 and < 20",
                "if x >= 10 and x <= 20",
                "if (10 <= x <= 20)",
                "if x => 10 and x=< 20 "
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following expressions correctly checks if the variable number is not equal to 0 in Python;",
            "answers": [
                "if number != 0",
                "if number <> 0",
                "if not number = 0",
                "if number not 0"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the output of the command bool(0.0)?",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False",
                "None",
                "Error"
            ],
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        }
    ]                 
